A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, International Division, Education and Public Policy Division, Office Files of Richard Sharpe FA557
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Future Program Planning Project, 1975-1976; III; 3.94 Cubic Feet
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 1. Hungry, Crowded World -- The International Food Policy Research Institute -- Food Policy Paper Summary, 1976 (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 1. Hungry, Crowded World -- Background -- Oscar Harkavy, 1975 December 10 (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 1. Hungry, Crowded World -- Staff Commentary, circa 1976 (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 2. Democratic Policy -- Silvert, Kalman H. -- "Democratic Non- and Anti-Democrats", 1976 (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 2. Democratic Policy -- Kothari, Rajni -- "Democratic Polity and its Future", 1976 February (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 2. Democratic Policy -- Calabresi, Guido -- "Democracy and the Allocating State", circa 1976 (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 2. Democratic Policy -- Shils, Edward -- "Our Society As It Is", circa 1976 (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 2. Democratic Policy -- Reid, Inez Smith -- "Democratic Polity and How It Works, With Special Reference to the United States", circa 1976 (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 2. Democratic Policy -- Shklar, Judith N. -- "Democratic Customs", circa 1976 (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 2. Democratic Policy -- Whitehead, Ralph Jr. -- "Notes on a Durable Present", 1976 March (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 2. Democratic Policy -- Background Paper -- Kelly, James A. and Kalman H. Silvert, 1975 December 15 (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 2. Democratic Policy -- Staff Commentary, circa 1976 (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 3. Values, Society -- Cardoso, Fernando Henrique -- "Values, Society, and Culture", circa 1976 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 3. Values, Society -- Tracy, David -- "Values, Society and Culture", 1976 February 28 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 3. Values, Society -- Miller, William Lee -- "The Improvement of the System Within the System", circa 1976 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 3. Values, Society -- Nozick, Robert -- "Values and Culture", circa 1976 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 3. Values, Society -- "Hamilton, Charles V. -- "On Values, Society, and Culture", 1976 March (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 3. Values, Society -- Background -- Sutton, Francis X., 1975 December 17 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 4. Knowledge -- Roche, Marcel -- "The Generation of Knowledge and its Spread to Change Society", circa 1976 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 4. Knowledge -- Ben-David, Joseph -- "The General and Spread of Knoweldge and its Application to Change in Society", circa 1976 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 4. Knowledge -- Kaplan, Martin -- "The Generation and Spread of Knowledge and its Application to Change in Society - For What?", 1976 February 17 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 4. Knowledge -- Background -- de Janosi, P.E. and F.C. Ward, 1975 December 10 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 5. Economic Growth -- Haq, Mahbub ul -- "Economic Growth and the Distribution of Economic Opportunity and Benefits Among Men and Nations", circa 1976 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 5. Economic Growth -- Johnson, Harry G. -- "Economic Growth and the Distribution of Economic Opportunities and Benefits Among Men and Nations: An Unenthusiastic Contribution Towards Predicting the Intellectual Stock Market", circa 1976 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 5. Economic Growth -- Gordon, David M. -- "Levelling the Hills and Valleys: Moving from Uneven to Even Economic Development", 1976 March (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 5. Economic Growth -- Sowell, Thomas -- "'Opportunity' and 'Growth'', circa 1976 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 5. Economic Growth -- Background Paper -- Bell, David and Marshall Robinson, 1975 December 10 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 6. Justice, Fairness -- Chalidze, Valery -- "Important Aspects of the International Defense of Human Rights", circa 1976 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 6. Justice, Fairness -- Cariola, Patricio, S.J. -- "A New Justice", circa 1976 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 6. Justice, Fairness -- Gale, Mary Ellen -- "Justice, Fairness, and Human Rights - Introduction: The Supreme Court and the Idea of Justice", 1976 March 1 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 6. Justice, Fairness -- Hastie, William -- Tape Recorded Remarks Re: Justice, Fairness and Human Rights, 1976 March 23 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 6. Justice, Fairness -- Tyler, Gus -- "A Paper on Human Rights, fairness and Justice for the Ford Foundation", 1976 February 5 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 6. Justice, Fairness -- Background -- Dodds, R. Harcourt and Robert H. Edwards, 1975 December 9 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 7. War, Peace -- Bull, Hedley -- "War, Peace and Cooperation Among Nations", circa 1976 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 7. War, Peace -- Nye, J.S. -- "International Conflict and Cooperation in the 1980's", 1976 March 1 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 7. War, Peace -- Brewer, Garry D. -- "Existing in a World of Institutionalized Danger", circa 1976 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 7. War, Peace -- Rubinstein, Amnon -- "A Look into the Future", circa 1976 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 7. War, Peace -- Background Paper -- Goodwin, Crauford D., 1975 December 1 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 8. The Individual -- Keniston, Kenneth -- "The Nature of the Individual and His or Her Fulfillment", circa 1976 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 8. The Individual -- Olds, James -- "The Pursuit of Happiness", circa 1976 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 8. The Individual -- March, James -- "The Nature of Things", 1976 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 8. The Individual -- Achebe, Chinua -- "The Nature of the Individual and His Fulfillment", 1976 March 11 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 8. The Individual -- Huxtable, Ada Louise -- "The Individual and His Fulfillment", circa 1976 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 8. The Individual -- Kozol, Jonathan -- "Building a New Conception of the Nature of the Individual and of the Limits of 'Our Human Nature'", 1976 February 26 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 8. The Individual -- Olson, David R. -- "On the Nature and Achievement of Human Competence", 1976 March 1 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 8. The Individual -- Background Paper -- Saario, Terry and Basil Whiting, 1975 December (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- Bundy, McGeorge -- "A Response to the Trustees on Proposed Priorities, Special Questions, and Remaining Hard Choices", 1976 November (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Consultant Files -- Achebe, Chinua, 1976 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Consultant Files -- Amsterdam, Anthony, 1975 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Consultant Files -- Bell, Joel, 1975-1976 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Consultant Files -- Ben-David, Joseph, 1975-1976 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Consultant Files -- Berelson, Bernard, 1976 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Consultant Files -- Brewer, Garry D., 1975-1976 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Consultant Files -- Buchan, Hon. Alastair Francis, 1975-1976 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Consultant Files -- Bull, Hedley, 1975-1976 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Consultant Files -- Calabresi, Guido, 1975-1976 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Consultant Files -- Cardoso, Fernando Henrique, 1975-1976 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Consultant Files -- Cariola, Patricio, 1975-1976 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Consultant Files -- Chalidze, Valery, 1975-1976 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Consultant Files -- Edelman, Marian Wright (incl. cassette tape), 1975-1976 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Consultant Files -- Gale, Mary Ellen, 1975-1976 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Consultant Files -- Geertz, Clifford and Hirschman, Albert (incl. cassette tapes), 1975-1976 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Consultant Files -- Gordon, David, 1975-1976 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Consultant Files -- Gordon, Kermit, 1976 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Consultant Files -- Gray, Hannah, 1976 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Consultant Files -- Habte, Aklilu, 1975-1976 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Consultant Files -- Hamilton, Charles, 1975-1976 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Consultant Files -- Haq, Mahbub ul, 1975-1976 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Consultant Files -- Haskins, Caryl P., 1976 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Consultant Files -- Hastie, Willliam H. (incl. cassette tapes), 1975-1976 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Consultant Files -- Huntington, Samuel P., 1976 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Consultant Files -- Huxtable, Ada Louise, 1975-1976 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Consultant Files -- Islam, Nurul, 1975-1976 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Consultant Files -- Johnson, Harry G., 1975-1976 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Consultant Files -- Kaplan, Martin, 1975-1976 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Consultant Files -- Keniston, Kenneth, 1975-1976 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Consultant Files -- Kothari, Rajni, 1975-1976 (Box 10)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Consultant Files -- Kozol, Jonathan, 1975-1976 (Box 10)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Consultant Files -- Legesse, Asmarom, 1975-1976 (Box 10)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Consultant Files -- Levitan, Sar A., et al., 1976 (Box 10)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Consultant Files -- March, James, 1975-1976 (Box 10)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Consultant Files -- Merton, Robert, 1975-1976 (Box 10)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Consultant Files -- Miller, William Lee, 1976 (Box 10)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Consultant Files -- Nozick, Robert, 1975-1976 (Box 10)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Consultant Files -- Nye, Joseph F., Jr., 1975-1976 (Box 10)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Other Consultant Appointments, 1976 (Box 10)
- Reports, Conferences, Papers, Reprints, 1977-1981; IV; 1.31 Cubic Feet
  - Reports -- Planning Papers, Book XXVI (June-July 1971) -- "A Portfolio of Large-Scale Possibilities" (1 of 9), 1971 June (Box 10)
  - Reports -- Planning Papers, Book XXVI (June-July 1971) -- "An Attempt at Self-Management on the Reservations" (2 of 9), 1971 June (Box 10)
  - Reports -- Planning Papers, Book XXVI (June-July 1971) -- "The Ford Foundation Management and Program Trends in the Fifties and Sixties" (3 of 9), 1971 June (Box 10)
  - Reports -- Planning Papers, Book XXVI (June-July 1971) -- "PAYE: Final Recommendations" (4 of 9), 1971 June (Box 10)
  - Reports -- Planning Papers, Book XXVI (June-July 1971) -- "PAYE: A Report to the Trustees" (5 of 9), 1971 June (Box 10)
  - Reports -- Planning Papers, Book XXVI (June-July 1971) -- "Report of the Internal Foundation Conference on Ford Foundation Programs in Europe" (2/24-25/1971) (6 of 9), 1971 July (Box 10)
  - Reports -- Planning Papers, Book XXVI (June-July 1971) -- "Proposed Budget, FY 1972" (7 of 9), 1971 June (Box 10)
  - Reports -- Planning Papers, Book XXVI (June-July 1971) -- "Toward a Revised Program Emphasis for the Division of Education and Research of the Ford Foundation" (8 of 9), 1971 September (Box 10)
  - Reports -- Planning Papers, Book XXVI (June-July 1971) -- "Pay as You Earn - Staff Papers on Income Contingent Lending" (9 of 9), 1971 June (Box 10)
  - Reports -- Planning Papers, Book XXXI (April-May 1972) -- Library Handbook (1 of 6), 1972 April (Box 10)
  - Reports -- Planning Papers, Book XXXI (April-May 1972) -- "Social Considerations and the Investment Process" by Bevis Longstreth and H. David Rosenbloom (2 of 6), 1972 April 15 (Box 10)
  - Reports -- Planning Papers, Book XXXI (April-May 1972) -- "Can Leadership Be Learned? An Assessment of the Work of the National Fellows Program" (3 of 6), 1972 April (Box 10)
  - Reports -- Planning Papers, Book XXXI (April-May 1972) -- "The Students Deserve Better" (4 of 6), 1972 April (Box 10)
  - Reports -- Planning Papers, Book XXXI (April-May 1972) -- "Two Organizations, Two Approaches, One Objective" Re: Grants to Capital Formation Inc. and Chicago Economic Development Corp. (5 of 6), 1972 April (Box 10)
  - Reports -- Planning Papers, Book XXXI (April-May 1972) -- "The Foundation and the Less Developed Countries - The Decade of the Seventies", 1972 April (Box 10)
  - Reports -- "Education and Development Reconsidered - Vol. One" -- Prepared for the Conference at Villa Serbelloni, Bellagio, Italy, 1972 May 3-5 (Box 10)
  - Reports -- "Education and Development Reconsidered - Vol. Two" -- Prepared for the Conference at Villa Serbelloni, Bellagio, Italy, 1972 May 3-5 (Box 10)
  - Reports -- "The Equal Rights Amendment: A Discussion", 1972 May 22 (Box 10)
  - Reports -- "International Research and Exchange Board", 1972 December (Box 10)
  - Reports -- "Little Cooperation on Co-ops", 1973 April (Box 10)
  - Reports -- "The Ford Foundation and Public Broadcasting", 1973 July 10 (Box 10)
  - Reports -- "Report of the Subcommittee on Education of the Telecommunications Task Force", 1973 July (Box 10)
  - Reports -- "Employment in Developing Countries" by Edgar O. Edwards, 1973 August (Box 10)
  - Reports -- "Education and Development - Agenda Papers" Prepared for Conference at Villa Serbelloni, Bellagio, Italy, 1973 November 1-9 (Box 10)
  - Reports -- "Problems and Issues Concerning Vietnam Veterans, Deserters, and Draft-Evaders", 1974 September (Box 10)
  - Reports -- "Choices Under a Reduced Program Budget", 1974 November (Box 10)
  - Reports -- "The Ford Foundation's Program in School Staff Development" and Additional Reports, Speeches Re: Public Education, by Edward Meade and Dick Lacey; Grants, 1974-1975 (Box 10)
  - Reports Re: Educational Research by Robert G. Myers, 1975 (Box 10)
  - Reports -- "Report of the Mission on Basic Education to Agencies Participating in the Bellagio Education Meetings" by Richard S. Sharpe and Jinapala Alles, 1975 March (Box 10)
  - Reports -- "Capacity Building in Planning and Research" for Meeting on Assistance to Education (Sep 16-18, 1975) by David Bell, 1975 September 18 (Box 10)
  - Reports -- "Education Research - The Promise and the Problem" by Harold Howe II, 1976 April 21 (Box 10)
  - Reports -- "Implementation of the Agrarian and Educational Reforms in Peru" Prepared for Conference in Texas (Apr 29-May 1, 1976) by Peter S. Cleaves (Box 10)
  - Reports -- Bellagio Papers Re: Educational Research and Development, 1976 (Box 10)
  - Reports -- "Federal Agencies and Urban Segregation - Steps Toward Coordinated Action" by Gary Orfield, 1978 August (Box 10)
  - Reports -- PIACT Papers, "Evaluation of the Safety of Modern Contraceptives in Developing Countries" by Olivia Schieffelin Nordberg and Linda E. Atkinson, 1979 January (Box 10)
  - Reports -- International Division Conference (Mar 21-24, 1979) -- Papers Re: Division Management, Programs, and Geographic Spread (Box 10)
  - Reports (research funded by Ford Foundation) -- "La Reproduccion y el Bienestar Humano: Un Desafio a la Investigacion", 1977 June (Box 10)
  - Reports (research funded by Ford Foundation) -- Manpower Demonstration Research Corporation -- Summary, Findings and Recommendations from National Supported Work Demonstration, 1980 (Box 10)
  - Reports (research funded by Ford Foundation) -- "A Directory of Selected Women's Research and Policy Centers", 1981 July (Box 10)
  - Ford Foundation Reprints -- "Foundations and Public-Private Ventures" by Franklin Thomas, 1979 (Box 10)
  - Ford Foundation Reprints -- "Minorities and Housing: Are the Doors Really Open?" by Robert Chandler, 1979 July-August (Box 10)
  - Ford Foundation Reprints -- "A Tale of Three Cities: Boston, Birmingham, Hartford", 1981 (Box 10)
  - Ford Foundation Reprints -- "Minorities and Mathematics", 1981 August (Box 10)
- Education, Social Sciences and Public Policy Programming Files, 1960-1981; V; 3.1 Cubic Feet
  - Asia and Pacific -- Grant Evaluation -- Pilot Project in Educational Television in the Philippines, 1971-1975 (Box 11)
  - International Division -- Grant Closures and Grant Lists; Report, "Grant Monitoring and Project Evaluation" by Curt Wolters, 1974 (Box 11)
  - International Division -- "Field Office Program Development Strategies in Education: Action vs. Research" by Richard S. Sharpe, undated (Box 11)
  - International Division -- Management and Operations -- Memoranda Re: Grant Actions, Budget Process, Programming, etc., 1971-1976 (Box 11)
  - International Educational Development -- Memoranda, 1975-1976 (Box 11)
  - Intergovernmental Conference on Cultural Policies in Africa -- Unesco Conference (Accra, Oct 27-Nov 6, 1975) -- General Information, papers, etc. (Box 11)
  - Intergovernmental Conference on Communication Policies in Latin America and the Caribbean -- Unesco Conference (Costa Rica, July 12-21, 1976), 1976 July (Box 11)
  - African Education and Ford Foundation Programming, 1974-1976 (Box 11)
  - Conference of Ministers of Education of African Member States (Jan 27-Feb 4, 1976) -- Memoranda, Reports (1 of 2), 1975-1976 (Box 11)
  - Conference of Ministers of Education of African Member States (Jan 27-Feb 4, 1976) -- Memoranda, Reports (2 of 2), 1975-1976 (Box 11)
  - Ghana -- Accra Office -- Quarterly Reports, 1970-1971 (Box 11)
  - Nigeria -- West Africa Regional Office -- Annual Report, 1968 (Box 11)
  - Nigeria -- West Africa Regional Office -- Annual Report, 1969 (Box 11)
  - Nigeria -- West Africa Regional Office -- Annual Report, 1970 (Box 11)
  - Nigeria -- West Africa Regional Office -- Quarterly Reports and Memoranda, 1970-1971 (Box 11)
  - Nigeria -- Vocational Improvement Centres -- Manuals Prepared by Ford Foundation Seminars, 1973 (Box 11)
  - Nigeria -- Education -- "Report on the Supply of Secondary Level Teachers in English-Speaking Africa" (Ford Foundation funded), 1973 (Box 11)
  - Nigeria -- Education, 1971-1972 (Box 11)
  - Nigeria -- Education -- "Investment in Education" Report (background information), 1960 (Box 11)
  - Nigeria -- Education -- Public Service Review Commission, 1973 (Box 11)
  - Reports -- "Governmental Population Policies in West Africa" by Davidson R. Gwatkin, 1970 December (Box 11)
  - Reports -- "Ghana and the Ford Foundation in the 1960s and 1970s" by David R. Smock, 1971 February (Box 11)
  - Reports -- "Studies in National Unity in West African Countries" by David R. Smock, 1971 February (Box 11)
  - Reports -- "Evaluation of the Northern Nigeria Teacher Education Project (640-0451 and 640-0451A) by Ross E. Bigelow, 1971 February 15 (Box 11)
  - Reports -- "Libraries in Nigeria" by Philip Rappaport for Ford Foundation Seminar (March 15-17, 1971), 1971 March (Box 11)
  - Reports -- "Staff Development at Four West African Universities"/"An Evaluation of Ford Foundation Staff Development Grants" by John J. Stremlau and Carolyn C. Stremlau, 1973 December (Box 11)
  - Reports -- "Report on the Conference of Ministers of Education of African States" by Melvin J. Fox, 1976 March 16 (Box 11)
  - Reports Re: Education, Development and Manpower Programs in Africa (not Ford Foundation reports), 1966-1974 (Box 11)
  - Reports Re: West African Education and University Programs and Plans, and Ford Foundation West Africa Regional Office 1973 Budget, 1971-1972 (Box 11)
  - Nairobi Office Budget Projections, 1981 May (Box 11)
  - Nairobi Office/Eastern and Southern Africa Programs and Studies Re: Population, Health, Nutrition (1 of 2), 1977-1981 (Box 11)
  - Nairobi Office/Eastern and Southern Africa Programs and Studies Re: Population, Health, Nutrition (2 of 2), 1977-1981 (Box 12)
  - Nairobi -- "Population Studies and Research Institute - University of Nairobi - The First Four Years" by John F. Kantner and Ozzie G. Simmons, 1981 June (Box 12)
  - Report on Trip to Pakistan Re: Study of Women's Educational Opportunities and Social Roles by Audrey Smock (Nairobi Office), 1976 October (Box 12)
  - Unesco Seminar on Educational Planning and Administration (in Africa), 1970 April 13-18 (Box 12)
  - Educational Broadcasting Conference in Kuwait (Mar 1-5, 1975) (Box 12)
  - Tel Aviv University School of Education -- Research Proposals to Ford Foundation, 1976 February (Box 12)
  - Notebooks -- Mexico and Chile, 1979-1980 (Box 12)
  - Notebooks -- Colombia and Peru I, circa 1980 (Box 12)
  - Notebooks -- Kenya I, undated (Box 12)
  - Notebooks -- Miscellaneous (1 of 2), undated (Box 12)
  - Notebooks -- Miscellaneous (2 of 2), undated (Box 12)
  - Bill Moyers' Journal -- "The New Equality: How Much and For Whom?" WNET Public Television, 1976 February 29 (Box 12)
  - Reports -- "Libraries and Library Development in Nigeria" by Philip Rappaport, 1971 December; Oversize. (Box 13)